<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tayyabali Sayyad</title>
    <link>http://tayyabali.in/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tayyabali Sayyad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 14:03:59 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tayyabali.in/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Origami Exhibition Visit - Thane, Mumbai.</title>
      <link>http://tayyabali.in/posts/origami/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 14:03:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tayyabali.in/posts/origami/</guid>
      <description>I visited an exhibition of Origami in Thane. It was organized by the Origami Thane group. Origami group’s intention to involve students into craft so that they become creative and stay away from the addiction to mobile phones.
Few things about Origami 
 Ori meaning &amp;ldquo;folding&amp;rdquo;, and kami meaning &amp;ldquo;paper&amp;rdquo; Associated Japanese culture Folding paper to transform into a finished sculpture  
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favourite Books</title>
      <link>http://tayyabali.in/posts/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 14:03:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tayyabali.in/posts/books/</guid>
      <description> The Obstacle Is the Way: The Timeless Art of Turning Trials into Triumph - Ryan Holiday The Leader Who Had No Title By Robin Sharma Mastery By Robert Green Inspired by the book Tribes: We Need You to Lead Us The 10X Rule: The Only Difference Between Success and Failure  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favourite Quotes</title>
      <link>http://tayyabali.in/posts/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 14:03:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tayyabali.in/posts/quotes/</guid>
      <description>Work hard in silence, let your success be your noise – Frank Ocean
 If you will live like no one else, later you can live like no one else – Dave Ramsey
 If you don’t have time to read, you don’t have the time (or the tools) to write. – Stephen King
 You pile up enough tomorrows, and you’ll find you are left with nothing but a lot of empty yesterdays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liked Videos</title>
      <link>http://tayyabali.in/posts/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 14:03:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tayyabali.in/posts/videos/</guid>
      <description> TEDx Talk: Solving Every Problem in the World with Education    Why you will fail to have a great career | Larry Smith | TEDxUW    Why You Will Fail To Solve Important Problems | Larry Smith, University of Waterloo     </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>